（忆往昔）
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫科尔
Name's Cole.
跟你哥哥迪恩 是老相识了
And your older brother, Dean, he and I, we go way back.
就是那晚 迪恩·温彻斯特杀了我爸爸
And that was the night that Dean Winchester murdered my father.
我们在对抗的是重量级的巫术
We're talking heavyweight witchcraft.
而且也不是新生代的巫术
Not some new-age wickan water douser, either.
是古老的黑魔法
This is old world black magic.
满脸疖子那种
Warts and all.
我讨厌女巫
I hate witches.
他们总是把自己的体液吐的到处都是
They're always spewing their bodily fluids everywhere.
极其不卫生
It's downright unsanitary.
卡西迪奥 我们不能再回避明摆着的事了
Castiel, it's time we stopped avoiding the obvious.
汉娜 我们不能迷路
Hannah, we can't afford to lose our way.
这任务至关重要 一切的情绪 感情
This mission is everything. Emotions…feelings …
都是危险的诱惑
They're dangerous temptations.
（如今）
劳尔
Raul.
快想想怎么说吧 狄阿娜
You better think fast, Tiana,
情况看上去可不妙
'cause this looks bad.
对不…我愿做任何事
I'm sor… I'll do anything.
我会回去 补偿你
I'll come back. I'll make it up to you.
求你别伤害我
Just please don't hurt me.
这样
Now…
其他姑娘会怎么想啊
What kind of message would that send the other girls, huh?
狄阿娜 狄阿娜
Oh, Tiana, Tiana.
我倒想说很遗憾失去你 但是…
I'd say I'm sorry to lose you, but…
你这种货色多得是呢
there's plenty more where you came from.
[邪恶力量 第10季第7集]
这个呢 几个镇开外 牛死亡
What? This? Um, cattle deaths a few towns over?
或许是恶魔
A demon possibility or something?
不 上面写了
No, it says right there.
可能是因为干旱
It's probably just 'cause of the drought.
那我们来干什么
So, what are we doing here?
吃饭啊
Uh, reason's right on your plate.
利萨尔多餐馆 美国农业部首推
Lizardo's porterhouse… U.S.D.A. Prime.
从康涅狄格州到地堡
It's the only place between Connecticut and the bunker.
就这里能吃顿10块以下的好牛排了
you can get a decent steak under 10 bucks.
伙计 是找你这么急啊
Dude, you are blowing up. Who is that?
就是警报啦
Ah, it's just, uh, you know, these alert thingies.
什么警报
For what?
怪物什么的
You know, monster…stuff.
别 还给我
No. Give it back.
什么 怎么了
What? Wh-why?
这是隐私…什么的
Because privacy… and stuff.
隐…
Oh, priv…
（迪恩·温彻斯特）
你在用约炮应用
You're on a dating app?
对 而且告诉你 没试过别急着否认
Yeah, and you know what? Don't knock it until you try it.
好账户名啊 迪恩 英帕拉67
Nice screen name, Dean… impala67.
够了 还给我 快点
All right, give it back. Come on.
夏琳啊
Shaylene, huh?
迪恩 你们都聊了一百万条了
Dean, there are like a million messages here.
是啊 看看她的照片
Yeah, uh, check out her pic.
（夏琳·约翰逊）
好吧
Okay.
好吧 她很性感
Um, okay. She's hot.
- 但是 - 但是什么
- But… - "But, " what?
她似乎…
But she seems, um…
有点…好上
Kind of…available.
太好上了
Like, too available.
「亲爱的 你想要什么都行
"Oh, baby, whatever you want.
我光想着你都欲火焚身「
I'm burning up just thinking about you."
后面更猥琐
They get raunchier.
是啊 看出来了
Yeah. Yeah, I… I see that.
简直是越写越露骨
It's like a, uh… like a penthouse letter.
是啊 这不好吗
Yeah. Is that bad?
不是不好 迪恩 只是好得不真实
No, it's not bad, Dean. It's too good to be true.
难道一位漂亮热情的美国女人
I'm sorry, is it… is it so hard to believe.
会对我这样的人感兴趣
that an attractive, red-blooded, American female.
就那么难以置信吗
could be interested in someone like me?
你知道根本不能保证
You realize there's no guarantee.
「夏琳」真是夏琳吧
"Shaylene" is even Shaylene.
说不定
I mean, for all you know,
那可能是个加拿大卡车司机 布鲁斯呢
it could be some… Canadian trucker n-named Bruce.
你觉得那像是布鲁斯吗
That look like a Bruce to you?
我们开车绕路8小时 就为了方便你滚床单
We… we detoured eight hours so you could get laid?
没错
Yeah. Yeah.
对了 午饭我请
Oh, and, uh, you know what? Lunch is on me.
别等我了
And, uh…don't wait up.
打扰了
Excuse me.
越来越容易了
It's getting easier.
艾萨克自愿回去了 甚至没有抵抗
Isaac came back willingly… didn't even resist.
但还有些天使在这里
There are still some angels down here,
但比较重要的那些都回去了
but the higher-profile rogues are back.
我们要把他们都找到 这是我们的任务
We find them all… that's the mission.
看 克里斯托弗·谢尔曼 牧师
Here. Christopher Sherman… pastor.
田纳西州当地报纸称
Local paper in Tennessee says.
他在自己的教区施展奇迹
he's working miracles in his parish.
是比喻吗
Figure of speech?
或许吧
Perhaps.
这是我们最好的线索了
The best lead we have.
除非我们能找到更好的线索 我们还是…
Until we find something stronger, we should…
去看看吧
…uh…check it out.
汉娜
Hannah?
嗯
Yes?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我要去冲澡
I'm taking a shower.
我们不需要冲澡
We don't need to shower.
我知道
I know.
你…
Are you…
这样让你困扰吗
Does this bother you?
困扰
Bothered?
没有啊
I…I'm not.
那就好
Good.
我忘了
I forgot something.
我们还得商量条件呢
We still need to discuss my terms.
什么 规则吗 床上规则吗
Oh, like, rules? Like, sexy rules?
应该说是价钱
Um, more an issue of payment.
是啊
Yeah.
亲爱的 我以为你明白了呢
Sweetie thought you figured it out.
虽然我没说出口
I mean, shy of coming out and saying it,
但我觉得我表现得够明显了
I thought I made it pretty obvious.
嗯 我就是…
Yeah, yeah, no. I-I just, uh…
我有个原则
See, I have this code.
真男人不买女人
Uh, "No cash for ass."
那你走运了 亲爱的
Oh, well you're in luck, honey,
因为我不是想要你的钱
'cause I don't want your money.
我只想要件小东西
All I want from you is one little thing…
不是什么大事
A trifle, really.
说吧
I'm listening.
你的灵魂
Your soul.
我的灵魂
My soul?
这没什么的 亲爱的
It's nothing, baby.
谁知道灵魂是什么 或者是否真的存在呢
Who knows what a soul is, really, if it even exists?
我只知道 你说好 我的人就来
All I know is you say yes, my guy comes up,
你签个字 然后你和我…
you sign some papers, and then it's you and me…
就可以开战了
good to go.
就这样 直接把我的命签走
So that's it? Just…sign over my life.
就是个签名
It's a signature, baby.
一点文书工作跟肉体的欢愉比算什么
What's a little paperwork compared to absolute physical bliss?
你说得很有道理
Well, you make a strong case.
我喜欢我的工作
I love my job.
是吗
Do you?
是啊
Yeah.
我可不觉得你真心喜欢呢
'cause it doesn't look like love to me.
去取车 我结账
Get the car. I'll check us out.
（卡罗琳·约翰逊）
卡罗琳
Caroline.
我给你的信用卡设了警报
I… I put an alert on your credit card.
我看到你在这里刷卡了
Saw a charge here.
我开了整晚过来
I drove all night.
怎么样了
How we doing?
大家都准备好开心一下了吗
Everybody ready for a good time?
好了 在这里签名
Okay. John Hancock right here.
然后就可以开始玩了
Then we can get this party started.
温家双煞
Winchesters.
她什么都告诉我们了
She told us everything.
绑架 强逼卖淫
Abduction, forced prostitution…
即使对恶魔来说 也够下作的
It's pretty gnarly, even for a demon.
她有她的说法 我有我的
She's got her version, I've got mine.
骗子
Liar.
我猜猜 她去找的你
Let me guess… she came to you.
求你给她拉皮条
begging for you to pimp her out.
没错 因为她是哈佛毕业的 混得可好了
Yeah, 'cause that Harvard degree was working out so well for her.
还有多少姑娘 这生意有多大
How many girls are there, hmm? How big is this?
- 只有我和夏琳 - 他撒谎
- Just me and Shay. - He's lying.
有间妓院 我听到他打电话了
There's a brothel. I heard him on the phone.
他们告诉我你是什么了 地狱的恶魔
They told me what you are… a demon from hell.
那也比街上的渣滓强
Beats trash from the street.
承认吧 小妞 要不是我
Face it, missy… without me,
你不出一年就会死于吸毒或更糟
you would've been dead of drugs or worse in a year.
老实说 这个贱婊该感谢我
Frankly, this little ho should be thanking me.
好吧 这下可好
Okay. Well, that just happened.
是啊 他是我们查到妓院地址的最好机会
Yeah, and he was our best shot at the location of the brothel.
你知道妓院在哪吗
Do you have any idea where it is?
不知道 但是
No, but, um…
我看到他在酒吧发这个
I saw him give these out at the bars.
（劳尔香坊 威利斯大街1482号）
你说什么
What did you say?
我说「你要是那么喜欢 自己穿好了」
I said, "If you like it so much, why don't you wear it?"
她不肯穿你选的衣服
She won't wear the clothes you picked.
怎么办
What should I do?
杰拉德 你说呢
Gerald, what do you think?
别留伤痕
Don't leave any marks.
女士 我觉得你走错地方了
Hey, lady, I think you're in the wrong place.
这不是劳尔香坊吗
This is Raul's girls, isn't it?
好有趣的名字
Clever name, by the way.
抱歉 但我们现在不招人
Sorry, but we're not hiring at the moment.
无意冒犯 但即使我们招
And, no offense, but even if we were,
你也有点老了
you're a little…old.
除非你是来消费的
Unless you're here as a customer.
无意冒犯你家姑娘
No disrespect to your girls,
但我宁可死 也不愿跟你这种肮脏的东西
but I'd sooner die than do business of any kind.
做交易
with filth like you.
你
You.
老大
Boss?
姑娘们 你们往后站站吧
Ladies, you may want to stand back.
接下来会很不好看
This will get messy.
虽说这不算是最开胃的事
Hardly the most appetizing process in the world,
但杀恶魔 总让我觉得饿
but killing demons always makes me hungry.
你们来吗
You coming?
你们完全可以留下
I mean, you're welcome to stay here.
太好了
Fabulous!
卡罗琳 你都失踪一年了
Caroline, you've been gone a year.
完全消失
Disappeared.
我不知道你出了什么事
I don't know what's happened to you,
我不知道谁蛊惑了你
I don't know who's gotten into your head,
但这里绝对有问题
but something's going on,
我不弄明白不会走的
and I'm not walking away till I know what.
的确是有原因的 这一切都是有原因的
Well, there is a reason, an answer for all of this.
- 那就告诉我 - 不行
- Th-then tell me. - I can't.
你不会理解的
You wouldn't understand.
那我就哪都不去
Then I'm not going anywhere.
我在车那边等了好久 但前台说…
I waited at the car, but the desk man said…
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
这是乔
This is Joe…
我丈夫
…my husband.
这人是谁
Who is this guy?
他…
He…
你是说 你们是一对儿吗
You saying you're…together?
什么
What?
是的
Yes.
我抛下你 就是为了他
I left you. For him.
他就是原因
He's the reason.
不
No.
不 我不信
No, I don't believe it.
就这家伙 就你
This guy? You?
不对…
No, there's something…
你不是那种人
You're not that kind of person, okay?
你不会那么做的
You wouldn't do that.
你不可能那么做
You couldn't do that.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们走吧
Let's go.
居然有人抢在我们之前杀了这混蛋劳尔
Can't believe somebody got to kill this Raul tool before we could.
- 查看身份证 - 好
- Check I.D.s. - All right.
迪恩
Uh, Dean,
看上去 闻上去
from the look and…smell of it,
完全是恶魔
pure demon.
这应该就是劳尔
I think this is Raul.
怎么 他自己吐死的吗
What? Did he puke himself to death?
是啊
Yeah, literally.
好吧
Okay, so…
这里发生了点事
Something went down here.
他们僵持了一下
There was a standoff.
一个恶魔化烟走了而劳尔
One demon smokes out and Raul…
什么东西能这么杀恶魔啊
What can even kill a demon like this?
看来
Apparently…
是女巫
A witch.
女士 我们来这儿做什么
Ma'am, why are we here?
我以为你们一定饿了
I thought you'd be hungry.
那个混蛋劳尔不会好好给你们饭吃吧
I doubt that swine Raul fed you properly.
是啊
Yeah, but…
但我们不该来这种地方
we don't belong here.
抱歉打扰了 女士
Apologies for the interruption, ma'am.
又这么叫我
That word again.
但是贻贝餐厅
But I'm afraid that the Bistro Des Moules.
有严格的着装要求
has a very strict dress code,
衣着标准
a sartorial standard.
而你们中有几位不满足这一标准
certain members of your party fall well short of.
我们能走了吧
Now can we go?
待在你的座位上 我们哪都不去
Stay in your seats. We're not going anywhere.
什么
Excuse me?
你没听错
You heard me.
[咒语]
95年库克香槟 很好的年份
A Krug '95… an excellent vintage.
我们一点心意
With our compliments, of course.
这太赞了
This is awesome.
你怎么做到的
How did you do it?
魔法
Magic.
杰拉德
Gerald…
一家妓院
A bordello?
你以我的名义开了家妓院
You opened a whorehouse in my name?
严格说 那里是叫劳尔香坊
Well, technically, the place was called Raul's girls,
但是 是的
but…yes.
劳尔说…
Look, Raul said that…
劳尔说了啊
Oh, Raul said?
您上月颁布的政令
Your decree last month…
灵魂交易在与阿比顿一战后严重不足
Soul deals way down after the war with Abaddon.
说要我们开阔思路
Said that you were looking for proactive.
主动想办法把数字搞上去
and out-of-the-box strategies to get numbers back up.
那你就和你的朋友把我拉进性行业了
So, you and your half-wit pal threw me into the sex trade?
我是邪恶 但那太俗了
I'm evil. That's just tacky.
我们想问您意见的
We tried running it past you,
但我们当时得知您不见人
but we were told you weren't taking meetings,
您心不在这边
that you were distracted.
我是说 您忙
I mean, busy.
这女巫轻松干掉了劳尔
Look, this witch took Raul down like that.
整个生意一下就完了
Whole operation… kaput.
我化烟跑了
I smoked out.
逃了
Ran away.
附身在我能找到的最近的肉身上
Possessed the nearest meatsuit I could find.
看来是的
Apparently so.
因为我觉得该通报您一声
Because I thought that you should know what happened.
这样的过分行为
Act of aggression like that.
您应该不会容忍
didn't seem like something you could let stand.
有了
Here we go.
看来在18世纪
So it looks like in the 18th century,
有多起巫术杀死恶魔的案例
there were accounts of demons killed by witchcraft.
恶魔都被一道咒语制服了
Apparently they were vanquished by a spell.
咒语叫做：[拉丁文]
called defigere et depurgare,
这是拉丁文
which is latin for.
意味「束缚 清除」
"to bind and purge."
你觉得就是这种咒语干掉了劳尔吗
You think that's the same kind of spell that took out Raul?
听上去是它
Sounds like it.
但就我查到的
But from what I can tell,
这咒语都300多年没人用过了
that spell hasn't been used in over 300 years.
而且 只有一个人用过它
And it was only ever known by one person,
就是创造咒语的女巫
the witch who created it.
是谁
That is?
罗威娜
Rowena.
大巫师团将
According to the Grand Coven,
世界上的巫师分为三类
there are three recognized kinds of witch in the world.
最常见的是借力者
Most common are the Borrowers…
为施巫术而汲取恶魔的魔力
those who harness the power of a demon in order to practice the art.
由于最近的经历
Owing to recent experience,
我看你们不会想那么做的
I doubt you'd have the stomach for that.
其次 也是最罕有的 是天生者
Secondly, and rarest of all, are the Naturals…
也就是
Those who are…
天生就有魔法的
born with the gift.
你就是这种吧
You're one of those.
这个
Well.
你猜对了
you are correct.
第三种呢
And what's the third?
学徒 没有天生法力
The Students… those with no natural ability.
但经过足够的练习和训练
who, with enough practice and training.
在大巫师团认可的导师引领下
and a Grand Coven-approved mentor to show them the path,
也可产生一点巫师法力
can eke out a modicum of witchly power.
那你能做我们的导师吗
Will… you be our mentor?
这个嘛
Well…
我是大巫师团最不认可的人了
I'm about as far from Grand-Coven-approved as it's possible to be.
他们很多年前把我驱逐了
They threw me out many years ago.
不认同我的手法
Disapproved of my methods.
说我的魔法太过极端
Said my magic was too extreme.
还禁止我使用魔法
I was forbidden from using magic,
吸纳学徒 建立巫师团
from taking students, from forming a coven.
自此之后 我一直在躲避那些混蛋
I've been on the run from those utter fannies ever since.
那你不能教我们吗
So, you can't teach us?
去他的大巫师团和他们可笑的规矩
Screw the Grand Coven and their silly rules.
你们俩跟着我 要什么有什么
You two stick with me, and you can have anything,
随心所欲
do anything you want whenever you want.
什么时候开始
When do we start?
很快 但不能在这里
Soon, but not here.
糟糕 我们该走了
Whoops. I believe that's our cue.
那是你做的吗
Did you do that?
他不会有事的
Oh, he'll be fine…
有工伤赔付嘛 你们来不来了
Worker's comp and all that. Are you coming?
叫救护车
Call 911!
我不害怕
I'm not afraid…
你就是个新手
'cause you're a noob.
我是你第一个吧
I'm your first.
所以你在拖时间
That's why you're drawing this out.
因为你在研究我
'cause you're studying me.
你在练手
You're training.
想要我说话 这点可不够
It's gonna take a lot more than that to make me talk.
你会说话的
Boy, you will talk.
你会说的 你会告诉我
You will talk, and you will tell me.
一切关于你的好伙计迪恩·温彻斯特的事
everything you know about your buddy Dean Winchester.
我们总得谈谈之前的事
At some point, we have to talk about what happened.
就是…
The, uh…
他不肯听 卡西迪奥
He wouldn't listen, Castiel.
他不肯放手
He wouldn't let me go.
我并不想伤害他
I didn't want to hurt him.
我本可以抹去他的记忆
I could've erased his memories, but…
但又觉得那样不好
it didn't feel right.
我以为如果他真相信我们是一对儿
I thought if he truly believed we were together,
他就会放弃
he'd give up.
这办法奏效了
And it worked.
可我为什么这么难过
So, why does it feel so bad?
你做得对
You did the right thing.
你伤害了他 但也给了他理由
You hurt him, but you gave him a reason,
让他可以向前看
something he could use to move forward.
理解他的失去
and make sense of his loss.
我两次把我的皮囊从他家人身边带走
I had to take my vessel from his family… twice, actually.
吉米·诺瓦克
Jimmy Novak.
他是个好人
He was a good man.
他有妻 有女 克莱尔
He was married, had a daughter…Claire.
但是呢
And?
虽然很艰难 但是没别的办法
And it was difficult, but necessary.
任务第一
The mission comes first …
一向如此
always.
我正值班 马蒂突然摔倒在地
Middle of my shift, there's Marty falling down,
抓着自己的脑袋
clutching his head,
就在那边地板上抽搐着
stroking out right there on the floor,
流汗 变红 就像…
sweating, turning red, like…
就像…
like…
就像他的脑子在沸腾
Like his brains were boiling?
（贻贝餐厅）
还有什么其他不寻常的事情吗
Was there anything else unusual?
比我们的领班在我面前暴毙还不正常的事吗
More unusual than our head waiter dropping dead in front of me?
在那之前
Before that.
说不好
I don't know, I mean.
我还觉得来了两个妓女
I thought getting two hookers in here.
就够非同寻常的
was pretty damn unusual,
但那是在我看到马蒂瘫倒之前
but that was before Marty keeled over.
两个妓女吗
Uh, two hookers?
就她们的穿着而言 应该是的
Based on what they were wearing, yeah.
就她们两个吗
Were they alone?
不是 她们是和一位女士一起来的
No. Came in with a lady.
多谢你抽空回答
Thank you for your time.
不 是蛮奇怪的
No, that is strange.
好的 我知道了 谢谢
All right, I hear you. Thank you.
看来那个女巫的确来过
So, it looks like our witch was here.
和两个新朋友一起
with two new friends.
真的吗
Really?
是劳尔香坊的吗
Raul's girls?
她想从她们身上得到什么
What does she want with them?
不知道 你从猎人网上得到什么消息了吗
I don't know. What'd you get from the hunter network?
有个达瑞尔在查一桩案子
This guy Darrell's been working a case,
一系列可怕的酒店凶杀案
a series of grisly hotel murders …
一起在肯斯汀顿酒店
one at the Kensington,
另一起在克利夫兰的华尔道夫酒店
another at the Waldorf in Cleveland …
尸体被捅伤 钉在天花板上
bodies stabbed, impaled on the ceiling.
听起来更像是变态杀人狂而不是女巫啊
Sounds a little more homicidal maniac than witchy.
达瑞尔也是这么想的
That's what Darrell thought, too,
直到他拿到尸检报告
until the autopsy came back.
真正的死因是…
Actual cause of death …
让我猜猜 是脑子被煮熟了吧
Let me guess … boiled brains.
没错 和这个服务生一样
Yeah, same as our waiter.
我必须承认 这位女巫很有钱啊
Well, I'll give this to the witch … she's got deep pockets.
肯斯汀顿酒店 华尔道夫酒店
The Kensington, the Waldorf,
还有这间餐厅
this restaurant …
可都不便宜
That can't be cheap.
是啊 动身吧
Yeah. Let's get.
去哪里
Where we going?
查查这一带所有的五星级酒店
Check out every five-star hotel in the area.
你怎么了
What's going on?
对不起 卡西迪奥
I'm sorry, Castiel.
我不和你走了
I'm not going with you.
我不干了
I'm done.
很难放弃…
It's hard letting go…
一个故事 一项任务
of a story, a mission.
可那些我们为了任务
But what of the humans whose lives we sacrifice.
而牺牲的人类呢
in the name of that mission?
他们怎么办
What of them?
我们过去总说人类是我们最初的使命
We always said the humans were our original mission.
也许现在 卡西迪奥…
Maybe it's time, Castiel …
该把他们摆在第一位了
time to put them first.
你这些想法是从哪来的
Where is all this coming from?
来到地球上
Being on earth,
和你一起工作
working with you,
让我有所感触
I've felt things.
人类的感触…
Human things …
激情 饥饿
passions, hungers.
洗澡的时候
To shower,
感受到水流过我的肌肤…
feel water on my skin…
想要靠近你
To get closer to you.
但这一切与
But all of that was nothing.
我见到他时的感受相比不算什么
compared to what I felt when I saw him.
她的丈夫 他的愤怒 他的悲伤
Her husband … his anger and his grief.
卡罗琳就在我身体里
And Caroline was inside of me,
对他大喊
screaming out for him,
想要回自己的生活
for her life back.
这些感觉
These f-feelings,
不是我的 不是我们的
they aren't for me, for us.
是她的
They belong to her.
我知道我该退出了
I know it's time to step aside.
再见 卡西迪奥
Goodbye, Castiel.
卡罗琳 我是…
Caroline, I'm …
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
我知道
I know.
好吧
Okay.
你们两个准备好做练习了吗
You two ready for some practice?
是谁
Who is it?
很可能是酒店经理
Probably the hotel manager.
来抱怨我没交钱
probably here to complain that I haven't paid the bill.
我给你们的咒语还在手上吧
You have those spells I gave you?
说到这个 我看不懂西班牙语
Yeah, about that? I don't read spanish.
那是拉丁语
It's latin.
读音在后面 亲爱的
Phonetics are on the back, darling.
「读音」
"Phonetics."
准备好
Get ready.
听我口令
And on my word…
等我们把你交给我们老大 你就等着受苦吧
You're in for a world of hurt when we deliver you to our boss.
那我们呢
What about us?
我不要再回到那个地方
I'm not going back to that place.
荡妇行动结束了
Operation Skank has been terminated.
你们俩要去的地方就是外面的垃圾箱
The only place you two are going is the dumpster out back.
这些人是谁
Who are those guys?
猎人
Hunters.
我们快走吧
Let's get out of here.
这不是出口
That's not an exit.
别担心 女士们 我们跟你们没仇
Don't worry, ladies. Our beef's not with you.
我们是来找这个女巫的
We're here for the witch.
罗威娜
Rowena.
能被认出来总是很高兴
Always nice to be recognized.
做点什么 念个咒语
Do something … a spell!
好主意
That's an excellent idea.
[咒语]
你对她做了什么
What did you do to her?
追 快追
Go! Go!
你做了什么 你对她做了什么
What'd you do? What did you do to her?
凶狗攻击咒 我们需要分散注意
Attack-dog spell. We needed a decoy.
但是…
But…
她会死的 就像那个服务生一样
But she'll die, just like the waiter.
可能吧
Probably.
很少有人能承受这种魔法
Few humans are built to survive magic like that,
而艾尔又很软弱
and Elle was weak.
但你不是
But you're not.
我们一见面我就看出来了
I saw it the second we met.
你很强壮
You're strong.
你说得对
You're right.
我的确是
I am.
- [咒语] - 闭嘴
- Occideris ingrat… - Not another word!
女士 你的运气用光了
Lady, your luck has just run out.
我很确定并没有
I'm pretty sure that's not true.
伙计 我们真得解决你的时机问题
Pal, we got to work on your timing.
放下枪 迪恩
Drop the gun, Dean-o.
好吧 她可能看起来没什么
All right, she may not look like much,
但是放她逃走 就是大错特错
But letting this one go … big mistake.
你听到他说的了
You heard the boy.
听着 我对我们上次见面时发生的事表示抱歉
Look, man, I am sorry about the last time we met, okay?
有很多事情 我都觉得很抱歉
I'm sorry about a lot of things.
我已经不是之前的那个我了
I'm not the same person that I was.
你根本就不是人
You're not a person at all.
我现在了解你们了
See, I know all about your kind now.
什么 听着
My kind? Listen …
我已经不再是恶魔了
I'm not a demon anymore.
那你杀死我父亲时 是恶魔吗
So, were you a demon when you murdered my father?
不是
No.
那你还是个魔头
Then you're still a monster.
我们开始吧
Let's go.
放我出去
Let…me…out!
不管她对你做了什么 你必须要与之抗争
Look…whatever she did to you, you have to fight it.
我做不到
I…can't.
不要动
Don't.
你在等什么 动手啊
What are you waiting for? Do it.
不
No.
我要一劳永逸地解决这个麻烦
Now, I'm gonna clean this mess up once and for all.
给我五分钟
You're gonna give me five minutes,
我们聊聊 起来
and we're gonna talk. Get up.
在那之后
After that…
如果你对你听到的不满意
If you don't like what you hear…
还想让我死 你就开枪
…you still want me dead, you take your shot.
我的工作 就是猎杀怪物
What I do… is hunt monsters.
你爸爸 科尔 你爸爸是怪物
Your dad, Cole … your dad was a monster.
你现在是这么说 但上次我们打斗时
Yeah, you say that now, but last time we fought,
你都不记得他的名字
you couldn't even remember his name.
2003年纽约州奈阿克 爱德·特伦顿
2003, Nyack, New York, Ed Trenton.
我在办案 三名死者
I was working a case. Three dead …
你父亲扯出他们的肝脏并吃掉
Livers ripped out and eaten by your father.
肝脏
Livers?
是的 那晚我在你们家找到了他
Yeah, I tracked him down that night to your house.
你说他是怪物
Well, you say he was a monster.
他是什么怪物
What kind of monster was he?
我不知道
I don't know.
从没见过那种 之后也没再见过
Never seen that kind before, never seen it again.
我只知道他那晚回到家中
All I know is that he came home that night.
想要杀人 可能是你
looking to kill … could've been you,
- 可能是你妈妈 - 不
- could've been your mom. - No.
他没那么做的唯一原因
The only reason that didn't happen.
是我去那里阻止了他
is because I was there to stop him.
我听到了他的声音
I heard his voice.
是人类的声音 他求你住手
It was a human voice, and he begged you to stop!
那是他的诡计
It's a ploy.
是怪物的花招
It's a monster's trick.
我知道你听到了什么
I know what you heard,
但你要知道
but know this …
那不是你父亲 科尔
That was not your father, Cole.
你父亲已经死了
Your father was already gone.
放下 萨姆 放下枪
Put it down. Sam, put it down!
科尔 没事的
Cole, it's fine.
迪恩
Dean?
放下枪
Put it down!
科尔 这里 我们还在说话
Cole, hey, right here. We're talking, okay?
我怎么能相信你
How can I believe you, huh?
How can I believe you?!
我这辈子 一直…
My whole life, I've been…
我明白
I get it.
那是你的故事
That was your story.
老兄 我也有
Look, man, I got one of those, too.
但是 这些支撑我们继续生活的故事
Okay, but those stories that we tell to keep us going?
有时 它们会蒙蔽我们
Man, sometimes they blind us.
会带我们走进黑暗 黑暗中
They take us to dark places … the kind of place.
我也许会狠狠揍个好人
where I might beat the crap out of a good man.
只为了取乐
just for the fun of it.
那些爱我的人
The people who love me,
将我从那悬崖边拉了回来
they pulled me back from that edge.
科尔 一旦你碰触到那黑暗
Cole, once you touch that darkness…
就永远甩不掉了
It never goes away.
真相就是
Now, the truth is…
我已经无药可救
I'm past saving.
我知道我会有什么样的结局
I know how my story ends.
要么是刃口 要么是枪筒
It's at the edge of a blade or the barrel of a gun.
问题是 会是今天吗
So, the question is, is that gonna be today?
会是那把枪吗
That gonna be that gun?
你有家人 科尔
You've got a family, Cole.
那晚我听到你打电话
I heard you on the phone that night.
我想他们需要你回去
I'm guessing they need you to come back,
他们需要你完完整整地回去
and they need you to come back whole.
我…
I'm…
（吉米·诺瓦克）
（失踪）
他说他要去哪
He say where he's going?
回家
Home.
罗威娜
Rowena?
跑了
In the wind.
你之前说的话
What you said earlier, back there,
说你已经无药可救 你是真的…
about being past saving … were you really …
我只是告诉他他该听到的话
I was just telling the guy what he needed to hear.
我们走吧
We better go.
温家双煞出现了 A队失败
Winchesters showed up. Alpha team went down.
但B队顶上了
But beta team's working contingency …
包围了酒店
Had a perimeter around the hotel.
我们抓住了她
We got her.
就在里面 经过了拷打
Right in there … tortured.
如果您愿意 我可以解决她
If you'd like, I could finish her off.
别笑得那么滑稽
Wipe that ridiculous smile off your face.
你想要什么 奖章吗
What do you want, a medal?
「谢谢你」收拾了你制造出的麻烦吗
A "Thank you" for cleaning up the mess you made?!
我的手下都神经失常吗
Everyone working for me touched?
一群粘人
Bunch of needy,
吵闹 没能力的幼稚儿
squalling, incompetent infants.
王终于来了
The king at last.
什么王 小人国的吗
King of what? Lilliput?
我早听说你很矮小 但是…
I mean, I'd heard you were short, but…
怎么
Well?!
开始啊
Get to it.
该给我致命一击了
Time for the coup de grace.
小男孩 你这是怎么了
Wee boy, is something the matter with you?
说不出话了吗
Cat got your tongue, hmm?
母亲
Mother?